[{"answer": "Hu", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Hi, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You don't?? I thought all guys had clubhouses", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "But dude, I don't have a clubhouse", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Just how many guys' clubhouses have you been in", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Give me a second, would you?", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I didn't snap at you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Don't snap at me", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You snapped at me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "This is a sweet spot for a clubhouse", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh uh, just that, mmmaybe when we're finished, my friend anduh my friend can come over and play", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Fine! And then we'll get girls to play Truth or Dare, too", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Fine", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Fine! That's fine", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Fine", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You need to shape up, mister", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't interrupt you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Don't interrupt me! You always interrupt me when I talk! Can't you see that ", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "There, you did it again!  He interrupted me again", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Okay, u", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Uh. ", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "And then, they'll ask,", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No no! You say,", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Man, Fat Abbot. What are you doin' on this side of the 'hood", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "School in summertime", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "G'oh", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Go where", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Umm. Dare", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "How about we give him my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Ii", "docId": "South-Park-Clubhouses.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Oh, maybe it was", "qsentId": 36}]